breathing is the greatest gift of life
to mankind but what happens when we
can't breathe
imagine being in a place where medical
assistance is very poor
and a patient's life entirely depends on
an artificial respiratory system
due to difficult terrain poor medical
infrastructure
and lack of connectivity life of people
in remote areas of our country
became quite challenging in this
pandemic
stabilizing and transporting patients
safely from a community health center to
a hospital
became a daunting task
ever since gowet's rock over nation
oxygen concentrators
became lifeline for patients who were
having breathing difficulty
and needed urgent medical assistance
at icici foundation standing with the
nation
has been our motto to identify locations
which required upgradation of medical
infrastructure
our teams crossed paths less traveled
we are in the process of providing over
1800 oxygen concentrators
across 17 states in the himalayan belt
and tribal regions of india
these oxygen concentrators would be
given to over 750 taluka level hospitals
which are located in difficult terrain
of our entire nation
for supply of quality oxygen
concentrators
we have joined hands with only credible
organizations
like bpl medical and philips with
quality product
and widespread network for after sales
service needs
so far we have distributed more than 350
oxygen concentrators
in various regions and managed to
stabilize patients
shortage of power supply in these remote
areas was another challenge
thus we are installing power backups
including a few rooftop
solar plants which will ensure a
continuous supply of power to the
hospitals
[Music]
icici foundation has helped close to 6
lakh underprivileged individuals of the
society
towards a sustainable likelihood we
would be providing technical training of
servicing oxygen concentrators
to underprivileged youth with the help
of our knowledge partner
bpl medical which will not only generate
livelihood opportunities
across the nation but will also help
people who are affected
due to this pandemic in breathing the
air our nature has blessed us with
[Music]
you